[
    {
        "question": "The peach blossom is the state flower for which U.S. state?",
        "answer": "Delaware -- No, it`s not Georgia. That would be the Cherokee rose. A viral disease nearly wiped out Delaware`s peach industry."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national flower of the United States?",
        "answer": "Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state flower of the U.S. state Georgia?",
        "answer": "Cherokee Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state flower of the U.S. state Iowa?",
        "answer": "Wild Prairie Rose -- The scientific name is Rosa arkansana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state flower of New York?",
        "answer": "Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state flower was chosen to honor pioneer women?",
        "answer": "Texas Bluebonnet"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Thousand Islands are located in what body of water?",
        "answer": "St. Lawrence River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brown University is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "Rhode Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is sometimes referred to as the Beaver State?",
        "answer": "Oregon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the most known animal species?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest religious monument in the world?",
        "answer": "Angkor Wat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest state high point in the U.S?",
        "answer": "Britton Hill, Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 25th island of Greece?",
        "answer": "Amorgos"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state rock of New Hampshire?",
        "answer": "Granite"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national flower of Wales?",
        "answer": "Daffodil -- Wales made the selection because it represents optimism and is one of the first seasonal symbols of spring."
    },
    {
        "question": "Besides English, what is the other official language of the Republic of Ireland?",
        "answer": "Gaeilge -- Also known as Irish, it is a Celtic language, and is historically one of the oldest languages in the world."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a common nickname for Ireland?",
        "answer": "The Emerald Isle -- Ireland is well-known for its lush fields, rolling green hills, and thriving farmlands."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano `Nyiragongo`?",
        "answer": "The Congo"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what continent were the Boer Wars fought?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Georgia city was Jimmy Carter`s hometown?",
        "answer": "Plains"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Australian island is named for the man who circumnavigated Australia and discovered New Zealand?",
        "answer": "Tasmania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sea lies between Greece and Turkey?",
        "answer": "Aegean Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what continent is the Balkan Peninsula?",
        "answer": "Europe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into what body of water does the Danube River empty?",
        "answer": "The Black Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Alcatraz Island located?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country would you find the Negev desert?",
        "answer": "Israel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is named after a British island?",
        "answer": "New Jersey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is considered the birthplace of democracy?",
        "answer": "Athens, Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country would you have to visit to enjoy a taste of Hymettus honey?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two US states do not share a border with any other state?",
        "answer": "Alaska and Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state was established by William Penn in 1681?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is known as the `birthplace of jazz`?",
        "answer": "New Orleans"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is services by McCarran International Airport?",
        "answer": "Las Vegas"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of Honolulu is located on what island?",
        "answer": "Oahu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What three colors are used in the flag of Texas?",
        "answer": "Red, white and blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Puerto Rico?",
        "answer": "San Juan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of China?",
        "answer": "Beijing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world`s largest country?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world`s second largest country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the four letter name of Thailand before 1949?",
        "answer": "Siam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What became the second independent country in the Americas after the United States?",
        "answer": "Haiti"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is Europe`s second largest island after Great Britain?",
        "answer": "Iceland"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to most sources, where is the world`s tallest unclimbed unclimable mountain?",
        "answer": "Bhutan/China"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you find on California`s Mount Lee?",
        "answer": "The `Hollywood` sign"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was George A. Custer defeated?",
        "answer": "At the Battle of the Little Bighorn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the southernmost continent?",
        "answer": "Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two countries noticed that they had the same flag at the 1936 Olympics in Berlin?",
        "answer": "Haiti and Liechtenstein"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is used in Hawaii as both a greeting and a farewell?",
        "answer": "Aloha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Sea of Tranquility?",
        "answer": "The Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has the longest border with Canada?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    }
]